<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>O-Despo</title><link>http://oliverdesposito.com/</link><description>Recent content on O-Despo</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 17:20:27 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://oliverdesposito.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Base Moji</title><link>http://oliverdesposito.com/projects/base-moji/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 17:20:27 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://oliverdesposito.com/projects/base-moji/</guid><description>Link To Page So one day you are sitting in math class day-dreaming. What do you day dream about? Well one day my answer to that question was a number base that used emoji instead of digits. Instead of using 0-10 this website uses emojis.</description></item><item><title>What This Blog Is For</title><link>http://oliverdesposito.com/blog/what-this-blog-is-for/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 16:22:03 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://oliverdesposito.com/blog/what-this-blog-is-for/</guid><description>Why This is here I want to make cool things. They don&amp;rsquo;t have to take a particular form they just need to be cool. It&amp;rsquo;s my belief that by making this little corner of the internet for me to share my thoughts I will be better motivated to make those cool things. There are no rules here except my own and no expectations except my own. So I think I will be an ideal space to share what I love and do.</description></item><item><title>Art Place Holder</title><link>http://oliverdesposito.com/art/artplaceholder/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:43:59 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://oliverdesposito.com/art/artplaceholder/</guid><description>Art and such For hugo to render pages properly I have to have some content so here is a picture I took. This is a picture of the start case going to the WMUC radio station. It&amp;rsquo;s the on campus UMD radio station. When I tell you that this is a special place I mean it. If you are looking for a place you can be yourself and vibe this is it.</description></item><item><title>Sr Thesis</title><link>http://oliverdesposito.com/projects/srthesis/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:22:46 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://oliverdesposito.com/projects/srthesis/</guid><description>Evaluation of Deep Learning methods for Sentiment Analysis of Twitter Data Link to main page The link above takes you to my high school senior thesis. It was completed as part of my English class and took a few months to put together. While looking back there were things I would have changed overall I am very proud of the work I did on this project.
This is a brief summary that I wrote for my application to start up shell.</description></item></channel></rss>